Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - Communication Workshop (Calendar Item, PSA, Release) (Box Box 11)
  - Festival of New Plays (PSA, Release, Calendar Item) (Box Box 11)
  - Delta Sisters to Meet (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Patriots' Invitational, 1979 (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Meeting in Fairfax (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - F. Elliston (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Folklore Country Music (Calendar Item, Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Spring at GMU (Media Advisory) (Box Box 12)
  - Communication Hang-Ups (Release, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Jazz Concert (PSA, Calendar Item, Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Symphonic Winds (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Spring Concert (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Art Exhibitions (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - New Course (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Mexico Tour (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Black Art and Literature (Release, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - DePillars / Art (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Forensics Team Wins (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Number One Speaker (Box Box 12)
  - Northern Virginia Association of Historians (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Susan Richards Shreve (Calendar Item, Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Gerontology Certificate (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - "However" (Calendar Item, Release, Cutline, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - Budget Tour Visit GMU (Media Advisory) (Box Box 12)
  - Haight Exhibit (Calendar Item, Release, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - Graduation Feature Leads (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Fairfax Country Students to Debate (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - MANN Collection (Cutline, Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Paris Oboist at GMU (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Craig Koppie (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - GMU Summer Courses (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Nursing School (Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Women in Russian (PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - Graduation (Cutlines) (Box Box 12)
  - New English Department Chairman (Release, Cutlines) (Box Box 12)
  - Positions Filled at GMU (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Powers (Release, V.P.) (Box Box 12)
  - Economics Learning (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Industrial Education Degree (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Local Government (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Financial Aid (MISAA)- Release (Box Box 12)
  - BIO Elect Ran Microscope (Release, Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - MANN Collection Dedication (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - G. W. Godbold Award (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Physics Courses (Box Box 12)
  - BATS (Release, Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - NEH Awards (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Culture and History of Japon (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Higher Education (Media Advisory) (Box Box 12)
  - The Environment (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - "Nation's Attic" (Cutline, Release) (Box Box 12)
  - GMU Campus Tour (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - The Gunston (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Spikell (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Original Research (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Review: History Thesis (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Irving Berlin (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - TAC Number 3 (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - NVWP (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Arundo Donax Trio (Box Box 12)
  - GMU Summer Chorus (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - GMU Summer Concert (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 12)
  - CPB- Kelley (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Writers Courses at GMU (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Briskin (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - IGS Awards (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Laraine Correll (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Krug Reception at Johnson (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Anita Taylor (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Summer Commencement "Year of Child" (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Scroggs- Langford- F. Leads (Release, Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Festival Piano Music (PSA, Release, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - An Invitation to Northern Virginia Music (PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 12)
  - Doctoral Program (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Grants (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Summer Commencement (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - FTP Workshop (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - Powers Recreation (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Math Conference (Cutline) (Box Box 12)
  - Biology Grants (Release) (Box Box 12)
  - GMU Craft Classes is Clay Play for Kids, 1979 (Cutline- PSA) (Box Box 13)
  - Preserving Cultural Heritage (Release- Cutline) (Box Box 13)
  - Math Conference (Release) (Box Box 13)
  - African Art (Calendar Item, PSA) (Box Box 13)
  - Men and Machines- News Release (Box Box 13)
  - Outstanding Achievement (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Cancer (Calendar Item- News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Job Hunting - News Release (Box Box 13)
  - FTP Exhibit (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Teachers Working Dinner Program (Box Box 13)
  - Techniques of Arguing (Calendar Item, P.S.A) (Box Box 13)
  - Something for Everyone (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Social Problems (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Open Board Meeting (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Consumer Rights (New Release, PSA, Calendar Item) (Box Box 13)
  - Turnage- N.R. (Box Box 13)
  - BOV Appointments- N.R. (Box Box 13)
  - Irish Writer Reads at GMU- P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 13)
  - Eric M. Leeper (News Release) (Box Box 13)
  - Neil Simon Musical (PSA- Calendar Item) (Box Box 13)
  - GMU/ High Schools Concert (C.I.- PSA) (Box Box 13)
  - Sense of Adventure (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Theatre at the 1930s (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Classes Under Way- Cutline (Box Box 13)
  - Choosing/ Changin Careers (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - "Hap" Spuhler- Cutline (Box Box 13)
  - Einstein- (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Orient Art (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Choral Concert At GMU (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Grey Ghost (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Views of the Orient (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Fanny Ventadour Pot Luck for Writers (C.I., P.S.A.) (Box Box 13)
  - Career Workshop (C.I., P.S.A., N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Historians Meet at GMU (C.I., P.S.A.) (Box Box 13)
  - Indochinese Refugees (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Fanny Ventadour (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Indochinese Conference (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Naturalist's Award (N.R., C.L.) (Box Box 13)
  - GMU Law School Information Center (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - 18th Century Medicine (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Child Abuse (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - College Talkers Compete (P.S.A., N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - GMU Theater (Cutline) (Box Box 13)
  - Second Consumer Seminar (P.S.A., N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Alumni "Brown Bag" Seminars (N.R., P.S.A.) (Box Box 13)
  - String Repair Workshop (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - V.P./ Scherrens (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Speakers to Compete at GMU (C.I., P.S.A.) (Box Box 13)
  - GMU Jazz Group Presents "A Salute to Tired Blood" (Box Box 13)
  - Symphony Concert (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Basics of Photography (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Historians Meet (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - GMU Campus Ministry Sponsors Senator's Talk (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Chamber Music Concert at GMU (C.I., P.S.A.) (Box Box 13)
  - "College Q-Line" (C.L.) (Box Box 13)
  - Communications (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Music/ Physics (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Fashion Show (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Sacred/ Secular Songs Concert (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Mission to Mexico (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Edmund White (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Choral and Organ Music (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Arts and Crafts Fair (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Dance/ Fall Concert (N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Linda A. Ewen (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Pre- School Education (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Auditions for Noah (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Problems of Indochinese (N.R., C.L.) (Box Box 13)
  - Study of Seminar Recreation (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Conference- Letters to Editors (Box Box 13)
  - Christmas Offerings in Music (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Shin- Splint Syndrome (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Media Mental Illness (N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Awake and Sing (C.I.) (Box Box 13)
  - Third Credit Seminar (P.S.A., C.I., N.R.) (Box Box 13)
  - Writers' Conference and Literary Festival/ Black Writers, 1979 (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - First Vice President Antia Taylor (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Joselovitz (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Edmund White (C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - GMU/ NVCC Dinner (C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - BIS Exhibit (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - L.E. Boothe (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Debate Team (N.R., C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - Decker (N.R., C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - Indochinese Refugee Studies Center (C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - Forensics (N.R., C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - Holiday Closing (P.S.A, C.I) (Box Box 14)
  - Death and Dying (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - For Women Writers (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - High School Debate (P.S.A, C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - College Debate (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Creditors' Collection (P.S.A., N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Religious Literature (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Writer Commencement/ Speaker Moye (Box Box 14)
  - Good News for Writers (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Who's Who (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Spring Literary Festival (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Jewish Writers (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Spreading the Word (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Moot Court (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Audition- Musical Ensemble (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Poets Visit White House (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Writers' Conference (C.L.) (Box Box 14)
  - Potomac (N.R., C.I., P.S.A.) (Box Box 14)
  - Svetlanov (Pianist)- N.R., C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Commencement- Cutline (Box Box 14)
  - Annual Fund (Cutline) (Box Box 14)
  - Book World- Writers' Conference Literary Festival- Calendar Item (Box Box 14)
  - Spring Potopourri (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - 20th Century Music - C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Is the Water Fit to Drink? (Potomac Series)- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Explaining Income Tax- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - GMU Homecoming (C.I., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - The Washington Post Letters (Box Box 14)
  - Craft Classes (Calendar Item) (Box Box 14)
  - Preserving the Potomac (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Creative Weekend/ Conference (Reading)- News Release (Box Box 14)
  - Speakers' Registry (N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Forensics (P.S.A., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Black History Month (C.L., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Education Conference (N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 14)
  - Noah (P.S.A., C.L., C.I., N.R.) (Box Box 14)
  - Institute on the American Family- C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Quiet Riot- N.R., C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Jazz Ensemble Disco- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Cohelan Honored -N.R., C.L. (Box Box 14)
  - Foreman: Video- N.R. (Box Box 14)
  - GMU Piano Recital- C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Families Facing Change- N.R., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Spring Writers Conference and Literary Festival- N.R., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - What troubles Northern Virginia Families?- Media Advisory (Box Box 14)
  - Fledgling Lawyers Argue Space Case- Media Advisory (Box Box 14)
  - Annual Government Contract Seminar- N.R., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Blue Danube/ Hecht- N.R., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Consumer Seminars- N.R., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - When... Gallaudet Theatre- C.L., C.I., P.S.A., N.R. (Box Box 14)
  - Managing the Potomac- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Growing Together Conference- N.R., C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Spanish Speaking Survey- N.R., C.L. (Box Box 14)
  - Professional Pianist to Perform at GMU (Box Box 14)
  - Potomac River- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - International Week- N.R., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Paintings on Display Fenwick- C.I. (Box Box 14)
  - Careers in Music- C.I., P.S.A., N.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Career Data Workshop- N.R., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Potomac- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Forensics- P.S.A., C.I., N.R. (Box Box 14)
  - Paintings/ Sizemore- N.R., C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Senta Driver- Cutline (Box Box 14)
  - Literary Festival, 1980- C.I., P.S.A., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Music Oboe- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Senior Piano Recital- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Career Options for Women- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Maps, Greenland and Geography- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Consumer Seminar Real Property- C.I., P.S.A., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Dorothy Walker- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Irish-American Debate- P.S.A., C.I., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - What Is The Lost of The Potomac (Box Box 15)
  - Poet David McAleavey- C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Professional Helpers/ Human Relations- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - House of Blue Leaves- C.I., C.L., N.R., P.S.A. (Box Box 14)
  - Summer Session- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Irish Week- N.R., C.L., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Art of Summer- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Music and Song- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Dick Gregory- N.R., C.I., C.L., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - University Day (Box Box 15)
  - Iron-Clad Agreement- C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Health Fair Week- N.R., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Forensics (ANIEC)- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Help For The Helping Professional (Box Box 15)
  - Debate Team- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - The Music of Youth- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - Black Drama- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Russel Nye- Pulitzer Prize Winner (P.S.A., N.R., C.I.) (Box Box 15)
  - Artist and Religion- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Africa/ Health/ Geography- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - International Week Chinese Students- Cutline (Box Box 15)
  - New Courses- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Study Tour- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Mason Day (Not For As A Story)- Media Advisory (Box Box 15)
  - Original Music- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Asian Studies Consortium- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Dance Into Spring- N.R., C.L., P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - In Concert- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Harold Brown- C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Basie, Berlin Jazz Ensemble- C.I., P.S.A. (Box Box 15)
  - 'Hugged A book", Friends of The Library- P.S.A., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Symphonic Winds Concert- P.S.A., C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Founder's Day Address- N.R., C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Elder Hostel- N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Cushing, Presidential Intern- C.L., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - NVWP Grant - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Sundell /German Theater - C.L, N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - GMU Junior Recital - C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Violin Recital, Julie Lambdin - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Honor Society, Nursing - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Fraud, Consumer Seminar - P.S.A, N.R., C.I (Box Box 15)
  - Publications Win Awards - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Wilbert A. King, Obituary (Box Box 15)
  - Junior Guitar Recital - C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Fifth Forensics - N.R, C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - GMU Professors Receiver Awards / Grants - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Writer To Teach A GMU, Edmund White - N.R, C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - GMU Honors Alumni - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - law School / Accreditation - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Spring commencement - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Saslaw To Speak - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Small World - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Protecting V.A's Wildlife - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Puppets - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 15)
  - Communications - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Awards Ceremonies - C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Mary Cho, Fellowship Awards - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Summer Chorus Auditions - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Faculty Members Honored (Box Box 15)
  - Courses On Early years - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Martin Agronsky - C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Spring Rate Agreement - C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Bov - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - GMU Artists display Work - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 15)
  - Finney receives Godbold Award - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - FTP National Award - N.R. (Box Box 15)
  - Protecting Consumer - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 15)
  - Picnic, Flash (Box Box 15)
  - Spring Commencements - C.L. (Box Box 15)
  - Research Grants / Women's Traits - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Orientation Day - C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Northern Virginia heritage - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Bloodmobile - P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Snyder Retires - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Co-op Student honored - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Consumer concerns - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - McConkey Named Asst. V-P - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Summer Research Grants - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Historic Puppets Donates - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Clements - Alumnus Of The Year - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Journal Of Labor Research - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Graduate Degrees In Writing - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Conductor / Summer Chorus - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Historic Puppets / FTP - Med. Adv. (Box Box 16)
  - Nursing Honors - C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Terry Holman TV - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Law School Ceremonies (Jaworski) - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Briskin Elected To Red Crass Board - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Doctoral Education Coordinator Appointed (Beyer) - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Summer Graduation - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Power Out ! / Flash (Box Box 16)
  - Oppelt Selected Acting Dean CAS - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Two New Members To GMU Board - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Chorus Presents Summer Concert - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Craig Book On Black Drama FTP - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Premiere Of "Refugee" - M.A (Box Box 16)
  - Tombes Wins national Fellowship - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Johnson Speaks to City Chambers - C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Broadside - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Student On The Run (McGrady) - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - "Helping Professionals" (Counseling Workshop) (Box Box 16)
  - First Doctoral Students - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Lecturer Publishes Book (Tran) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Summer Chorus At Wolf Trap - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - GMU Theatre Presents, The Rimers Of Eldritch - C.I., P.S.A, N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - Books By The Boyload - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Sing Along With Brahms - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Black Photographer to Be Honored - C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Peking Visitors AT GMU - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - GMU Welcomes New Arrivals (Francescato, Boneau) (Box Box 16)
  - Faculty Lecture Series - P.S.A, N.R., C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Poet Laureate Reods At GMU - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Temporary Site For GMU Metro Campus Classes - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Annual High School Debate Clinic - C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Jr. High Students Exhibit Art - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Grant Awarded (Bonfadini) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Faculty Makes Music - C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Music Festival - P.S.A, N.R., C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Joworski speech At Law School graduation - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Musical auditions - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - Organizational Communication - New Course - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - ViewPoint (Harry Stopp) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - GMU Playwright And Encore (Joselovtei) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Arlington Rotary Scholarship - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - University Course On Terrorism - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Biologist Receives Grant (Hart) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Partners In Law And marriage (Law School) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Waiting For The Verdict (Law School) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - ABA Accredits GMU School Of law - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Public Relations Director Appointed - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 16)
  - University - Community Chorus Gives First Concert (Smith) - S.A, C.I. (Box Box 16)
  - New Doctorate In Education At GMU - N.R., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Writer's Club Brings Edward Honing To Campus - P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Robert P. Clark Faculty Lecture Series - C.I., N.R., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - GMU Hosts Forensics Tournament - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Hazel Recognized For Service To GMU - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Book On Basgue Movement by Robert P. Clark - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Conference Cont. Ed. For Engineers - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Irish Studies Committee Holds Annual Meetings - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - GMU And High School Orchestras Combine For Concert - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Friends of The Library Book Sale - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - New Asst. to The Pres. For Special Projects (William H. Cohn) - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Egerman To Coordinate GMU Publications - N.R. (Box Box 16)
  - Suicide Prevention Conference - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Handicapped Week At GMU - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 16)
  - Poet And Editor At GMU (Poul Zimmer) - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Children's Book Author At GMU (Lobel) - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Theatre Presents The Shadow Box - C.I., P.S.A, N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Jazz Ensemble Performs "Bebop" - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Forensics Team - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Black Women Portraits On Display At GMU - C.I., P.S.A, N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Dahlin lauded For Fund - Raising Efforts - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Staff Member Receives Award (Donnelly0 - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Education Grant to Work With handicapped - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Appoints Development Officer (Pickell) - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Hosts Great Eastern Forensic Tournament - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Columnists Talk At GMU - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Honors Nursing Chairperson - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Will Sponsor Debate Workshop - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - New Director of Alumni Relations - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Professor Studies Surgical Patients Spouses (Silva) - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Multicultural / Bilingual Educ. Center Receives Grant - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU To Host Annual Writers Conference / Festival - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Hirst Donates Lecture Series - C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Jones Appointed Head Acct. / Bus. Legal studies - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Music Careers Conference - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Post Reporters Conduct Workshop At GMU - C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - Supreme Court justice At Law School - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Economist Named to Society - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Holds International Day - C.I., N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - CUE Publicity (Bus Services) - P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - Friends Of The Library Book sale Post Publicity (Lampe) - C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Washington Post Reporter Speaks At GMU - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Exhibits Children's Book Illustrations - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - "Feminist Perspective On Sexual Liberation" - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Homecoming - P.S.A, N.R., C.I., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Careers In Science Discussed At GMU - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Teacher Certification hearing At GMU - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Informal Dance COncert At GMU - C.I., C.L., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - A Christmas Fanfare by GMU Choruses - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU's Chamber Orchestra Performs - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - George Mason Featured In George Mason Lecture - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU To Host VASPA State Conference - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Novelist Hilma Walitzer At GMU - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - fall of The Tropical Rain Forests - C.I., N.R., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Display Christmas Arts And Crafts - P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Forensics Team Maintains Streak - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Library Training Program Funded - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Student Artwork Display At Fairfax City Hall - C.I. (Box Box 17)
  - Nursing Programs Accredited - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Novelist Bausch Directs Writing Program - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - ASPA Conference Registration Deadline - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Doctoral Programs Dinner At Gunston Hall - C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Economists Tackle Bureaucratic Growth (Bentt, Johnson) - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Delegation Of Nurses from People's Rep. Of China Nursing Assoc. - C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Professor Publishes Book On Truman Cape (Garson) - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Master Of Social Work To Focus On Na. Va - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Williams Receives national Award - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Old Dominion Courses At GMU - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - World Conflict Resolutions Discussed At GMU - C.L., N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - GMU Student Attends National Business Conference (McCorick) (Box Box 17)
  - Graduation Features - Winter 1980 - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Nurses Institute To Cover Chemotherapy - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Helen Hill Miller Lecture C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - Murphey And Company to Dance In D.C. - N.R., C.L. (Box Box 17)
  - High School Student Debate - N.R., C.I., P.S.A (Box Box 17)
  - Colonial Christmas Celebration - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Christmas With Words And Music - N.R. (Box Box 17)
  - Let's Get Rowdy! (cheer leaders) - C.L. (Box Box 17)